<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Getting Started on</title><link>https://docs.pollen-robotics.com/sdk/getting-started/</link><description>Recent content in Getting Started on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 18:49:17 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://docs.pollen-robotics.com/sdk/getting-started/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Introduction</title><link>https://docs.pollen-robotics.com/sdk/getting-started/introduction/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 18:50:18 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://docs.pollen-robotics.com/sdk/getting-started/introduction/</guid><description>The SDK in a nutshell #
The Python SDK lets you easily control and program a Reachy robot. It is used to read sensor information (eg. force sensor, camera image or joint position) and send actuator commands (eg. target position, turning on a fan).
It is designed to:
let you start controlling your robot in a few lines of codes, allow to focus on your application and not on hardware synchronisation issues, facilitate fast prototyping and iteration.</description></item><item><title>Installation</title><link>https://docs.pollen-robotics.com/sdk/getting-started/install/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 18:50:10 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://docs.pollen-robotics.com/sdk/getting-started/install/</guid><description>How to install the Python SDK #
The Python SDK is a pure Python library. The installation should thus be rather straightforward. It supports Python &amp;gt;= 3.6 (older versions may work but are not officially supported). It works on Windows/Mac/Linux.
We recommend to use virtual environment for your development. They make the installation simple and avoid compatibility issues. They also come with their pip command.
From PyPi #
pip3 install reachy-sdk
From the source #
git clone https://github.</description></item><item><title>Hello World</title><link>https://docs.pollen-robotics.com/sdk/getting-started/hello-world/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 18:50:04 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://docs.pollen-robotics.com/sdk/getting-started/hello-world/</guid><description>Now you should be able to connect to your Reachy and check that everything is ok. As we spoiled in the previous section, to connect to your robot, you simply need to run the following code:
from reachy_sdk import ReachySDK
# Replace with the actual IP you've found.
reachy = ReachySDK(host='the.reachy.ip.found.')
Before diving into the next chapters that will guide you in the depth of what you can do with the Reachy SDK, here is a quick preview.</description></item><item><title>Finding Reachy's IP</title><link>https://docs.pollen-robotics.com/sdk/getting-started/finding-ip/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 18:49:56 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://docs.pollen-robotics.com/sdk/getting-started/finding-ip/</guid><description>The last required step before actually programing your Reachy is to find its IP address.
A small LCD screen should be installed in Reachy&amp;rsquo;s back to display Reachy&amp;rsquo;s IP address. You will need to take down its tee-shirt to see the LCD screen.
The instructions to display the IP address to the LCD screen is provided by the dashboard which is started at boot with the service reachy_dashboard.service.
If the LCD screen is not working, check out the page Find my IP section to learn other ways to get the IP address.</description></item></channel></rss>